

Contacts

- **+380938799327**
- Telegram
- **⇔** GitHub
- in LinkedIn
- ,♥, Kyiv, Ukraine

Tech Skills

- · HTML5
- · CSS3
- JavaScript
- · React/Redux
- · GII
- · Node.js/Express
- Swagger
- WebPack
- · Rest API
- · Scrum, Agile
- · Web performance optimization
- · Cross-browser compatibility

Soft Skills

- · Attentive to details
- Flexible
- · Customer-focused
- · Problem-solving
- · Excellent communication

Languages

- · English: Pre-intermediate
- · Ukrainian: Native

Ihor Nechai

Front-End Developer

Summary

I am a dedicated and focused professional with experience in HTML, CSS, JS, React, Git, Node.js. I would like to use my skills acquired while successfully completing the GoIT Full-Stack Dev program and working in a network engineering environment to be involved as a Front-End developer. I have a perfect command of HTML, CSS, Vanilla JS, I also have knowledge of writing backends on Node (Express server), I learn quickly and never stop learning.

Projects

Web Search for images [Git-hub] [HTML5, CSS3, JS, Notify, SimpleLightBox, Axios] Creation of WEB using external libraries. Role: Developer

WebStudio [Git-hub]

[HTML5, CSS3, Webpack (Parcel)]

Creation of WEB using HTML, SCSS (SASS) with responsive layout. Role: Developer

Internet Shop [Git-hub]

[HTML5, CSS3, JS ("Team project")]

Internet shop with modern design and with responsive layout, used HTML, SCSS (SASS), JS. Role: Team-lead, Developer

NYTimes News[Git-hub]

[HTML5, SCSS, JS, Api ("Team project")]

News Pages with NYTimes API, responsive layout, used HTML, SCSS (SASS), JS. Role: Scrum-master, Developer (Gallery, Pagination)

Backend for Pet site [Git-hub]

[Node, Express, MongoDB, Swagger]

Backend server on Express used Node, mongoose, JS. Role: Team-lead, Developer (Middlewares, Utils, Routes...)

Work Experience

Network Engineer Datagroup

February 2021 - 2023 | Kyiv, Obukhiv region

- Creating, implementing and maintaining computer networks in Obukhiv region
- Installing network hardware and software
- Monitoring and troubleshooting network performance for switches on the local and global network using the Unix system
- Acting as a mentor for Engineer Associates and team-leading to provide 24/7 customer support

Network Engineer Volia

February 2011 - February 2021 | Kyiv

- Provided designing, installing and configuring of TV services using ethernet technology
- Initiated and was responsible for maintenance of staff workload assignment documentation automated by Excel macros
- Ensured effective provision procedure of Service Desk software

Education

Go IT

Full Stack Developer

Sep 2022 - Aug 2023

Uzhgorod State Institute of Informatics, Economics and Law Automatic control system

2001 - 2004